# **Blake Printy**

Hartford, CT | Blakehprinty@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/blake-printy/ | https://blakeprinty.github.io/

### FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

My name is Blake Printy, I studied Computer Science at the University of Maryland, Baltimore County. I then joined WeCanCodeIT's full time bootcamp. I love learning new technologies and pushing myself to become a better developer.

#### **TECHNICAL INVENTORY**

Java • Spring • Thymeleaf • JavaScript • MVC • HTML • CSS • TDD • Agile (Scrum) • Object Oriented Programming (OOP) • JSON • React • Python • C++ • REST APIs • Responsive Design / Mobile • Relational Databases • Source Control / GitHub

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT EXPERIENCE/PROJECTS

[Personal Github address here]

We Can Code IT, Cleveland, OH Software Development Student, 2021

Planned, designed, and developed professionally programmed applications in collaborative team-based and independent settings, demonstrating the proficiency to earn Software Development Certificate.

**HabiTrack:** Web application used for allowing users to better themselves by tracking their habits, choosing whether to make or break them

Java, JavaScript, Single Page Web App, TDD, OOP, API

WordleSolver: Web application designed to help users solve the wordle of the day

Java, JavaScript, Single Page Web App, TDD, OOP, API

EatFit: Web Application that gives users recipes to try if they are trying to gain or lose weight Java, JavaScript, Thymeleaf, Spring, TDD, OOP, API

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE (WORK HISTORY)

FedEx Ground, South Windsor, CT (June 2021 - August 2021, February 2022 - Present)

Package Handler

- Pulling packages from the main belt
- Loading packages into tractor trailers
- Unloading packages from tractor trailers

Hometown Pizza, Ellington, CT (August 2018 - August 2021)

Job Title

- Delivering Pizza
- Taking orders both in person and over the phone
- Resolving customer complaints

# **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

We Can Code IT

Certificate of Software Development, 2022

University of Maryland, Baltimore County

Computer Science, 2020-2022